Center for Women in Government; Records ua685
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Director Records, 1981-2003; 1 cubic ft.
  - News on Women in Government, 1985 June (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - News on Women in Government, 1986 June (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - News on Women in Government, 1982 July (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - News on Women in Government, 1989 Fall (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Address labels for staff, former instructors, board, and former board, Undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Web Archives, 2010 February 18-2016 September 18; 6; 771 captures
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service. This page includes links to both the university's collection and the Internet Archive's public collection.
  Surface-level crawling of www.albany.edu is performed daily which should includes most top-level webpages. Separate targeted crawls of every albany.edu subdomain are performed monthly to attempt to gather all content. This includes: www.albany.edu, www.rna.albany.edu, www.ctg.albany.edu, www.ualbanysports.com, www.albany.edu/rockefeller, www.albany.edu/cela, www.albany.edu/asrc, m.albany.edu, library.albany.edu, events.albany.edu, cstar.cestm.albany.edu, csda.albany.edu, and alumni.albany.edu
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Web Archives
  - http://www.albany.edu/womeningov/ - University Archives collection, 2013 May 8-2016 September 18 (Web-archive 1)
  - WARC file for http://www.albany.edu/womeningov/, (please see https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_ARChive for more details), 2013 May 8-2016 September 18 (Warc 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in researching with web archives.
  - http://www.albany.edu/womeningov/ - Internet Archive collection, 2010 February 18-2016 September 18 (Web-archive 2)